blistergearreview.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Blister Gear Review - Skis, Snowboards, Mountain Bikes, Climbing, Kayaking

This website is referred to in these notices as the “Site,” and when “we”, “our” or “us” are used below, blistergearreview.com (Blister Gear Review) is referred to. End users are referred to as “you” below.

## **PRIVACY POLICY**

By visiting, accessing or using the Site and any linked pages, features, or content on the Site, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. You also signify that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by our [Terms & Conditions](http://blistergearreview.com/terms-conditions).

#### The Information We Collect

This policy applies to all information collected by or submitted to us on the Site. In some areas of the Site, you can order products and register to receive materials or communications from us. The types of Personal Information collected on the Site are your: Name **,** Address **,** Email address **,** Phone number, and Credit/Debit card information.

#### How We Use Your Information

We do not sell or provide your “Personal Information” to third parties, except as described below.

We may provide Personal Information to affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing it, though these third parties may only use your Personal Information to the extent required to perform their services on our behalf.

Your Personal Information is also used to contact you when necessary with regards to an order, a product, or content on the Site.

#### Security

Your Blister Gear Review account and Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security.

To prevent unauthorized access and maintain accuracy of information, we have put in place electronic and managerial procedures to protect and secure the information we collect online. We protect the security of your Personal Information whenever it is transmitted by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption, which protects the Personal Information you input on the site. We cannot guarantee that the security measures we have in place to safeguard personal information will never fail, or that those measures will always be sufficient or effective.

Credit card transactions are handled by third party institutions who receive credit card numbers and other personal information from the Site, verify the credit card numbers, and process transactions.

The use of your personal information by the third party institutions is subject to their own privacy policies. In the same way, the Site contains links to other sites, and we are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and computer; please keep your password secret and do not disclose it to others. You should be sure to sign off of your account after using a shared computer.

You also have the option to access the Site from your mobile or wireless device. We have no control over your carrier or network administrator’s policies, and the carrier or network administrator may have access to your Personal Information.

#### Changes to our Terms & Conditions or our Privacy Policy

We may change or replace our “[Terms & Conditions](http://blistergearreview.com/terms-conditions)” and/or our “Privacy Policy” at any time. You are bound by any changes to the [Terms & Conditions](http://blistergearreview.com/terms-conditions) and/or our Privacy Policy when you use the Site after such changes have been first posted.

_Effective Date: August 27, 2015_
